{"response_code":0,"results":[{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"A comet&#039;s gaseous envelope (which creates the tail) is called what?","correct_answer":"The coma","incorrect_answers":["The wake","The backwash","The ablative"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Botanically speaking, which of these fruits is NOT a berry?","correct_answer":"Strawberry","incorrect_answers":["Blueberry","Banana","Concord Grape"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"What does the scientific name of the Cambrian-Period sea creature Anomalocaris mean?","correct_answer":"Abnormal Shrimp","incorrect_answers":["Deformed Fish","Strange Crab","Anomalous Clam"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"What is considered the rarest form of color blindness?","correct_answer":"Blue","incorrect_answers":["Red","Green","Purple"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"What is the scientific name of the red fox?","correct_answer":"Vulpes Vulpes","incorrect_answers":["Vulpes Redus","Red Fox","Vulpes Vulpie"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which of these chemical compounds is NOT found in gastric acid?","correct_answer":"Sulfuric acid","incorrect_answers":["Hydrochloric acid","Potassium chloride","Sodium chloride"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"How many types of quarks are there in the standard model of physics?","correct_answer":"6","incorrect_answers":["2","3","4"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which is not a type of neuron?","correct_answer":"Perceptual Neuron","incorrect_answers":["Sensory Neuron","Motor Neuron","Interneuron"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which of these is a semiconductor amplifying device?","correct_answer":"transistor","incorrect_answers":["tube","diode","P-N junction"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"What is isobutylphenylpropanoic acid more commonly known as?","correct_answer":"Ibuprofen","incorrect_answers":["Morphine","Ketamine","Aspirin"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"An organic compound is considered an alcohol if it has what functional group?","correct_answer":"Hydroxyl","incorrect_answers":["Carbonyl","Alkyl","Aldehyde"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which is the chemical name of H2O?","correct_answer":"Dihydrogen Monoxide","incorrect_answers":["Ammonium chloride","Anhydrous Sodium Carbonate","Manganese dioxide"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which of the following is the term for &quot;surgical complications resulting from surgical sponges left inside the patient&#039;s body?","correct_answer":"Gossypiboma","incorrect_answers":["Gongoozler","Jentacular","Meupareunia"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"If you planted the seeds of Quercus robur what would grow?","correct_answer":"Trees","incorrect_answers":["Flowers","Vegtables","Grains"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Burning which of these metals will produce a bright white flame?","correct_answer":"Magnesium","incorrect_answers":["Copper","Lithium","Lead"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"What nucleotide pairs with guanine?","correct_answer":"Cytosine","incorrect_answers":["Thymine","Adenine","Uracil"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Coulrophobia is the irrational fear of what?","correct_answer":"Clowns","incorrect_answers":["Cemeteries","Needles","Tunnels"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Autosomal-dominant Compelling Helio-Ophthalmic Outburst syndrome is the need to do what when seeing the Sun?","correct_answer":"Sneeze","incorrect_answers":["Cough","Yawn","Hiccup"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which of the following is a major muscle of the back?","correct_answer":"Trapezius","incorrect_answers":["Trapezium","Trapezoid","Triquetrum"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"What causes the sound of a heartbeat?","correct_answer":"Closure of the heart valves","incorrect_answers":["Contraction of the heart chambers","Blood exiting the heart","Relaxation of the heart chambers"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which scientific unit is named after an Italian nobleman?","correct_answer":"Volt","incorrect_answers":["Pascal","Ohm","Hertz"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"What is &quot;Stenoma&quot;?","correct_answer":"A genus of moths","incorrect_answers":["A combat stimulant from WW2","A type of seasoning","A port city in the carribean"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"What is the molecular formula of Glucose?","correct_answer":"C6H12O6","incorrect_answers":["C2H4O2","K+","CH4"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which of these animals belongs in class Chondrichthyes?","correct_answer":"Great white shark","incorrect_answers":["Octopus","Killer whale","Catfish"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Folic acid is the synthetic form of which vitamin?","correct_answer":"Vitamin B","incorrect_answers":["Vitamin A","Vitamin C","Vitamin D"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"What element on the periodic table has 92 electrons?","correct_answer":"Uranium","incorrect_answers":["Sulfur","Hydrogen","Iron"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"How long is a light-year?","correct_answer":"9.461 Trillion Kilometres","incorrect_answers":["1 AU","105.40 Earth-years","501.2 Million Miles"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"What is the unit of electrical inductance?","correct_answer":"Henry","incorrect_answers":["Weber","Coulomb","Mho"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which of the following is NOT a word used to describe an earthquake?","correct_answer":"Drop-slide","incorrect_answers":["Foreshock","Strike-slip","Temblor"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"&quot;The Big Bang Theory&quot; was first theorized by a priest of what religious ideology?","correct_answer":"Catholic","incorrect_answers":["Christian","Jewish","Islamic"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Where in the human body is the Pineal Gland located?","correct_answer":"Brain","incorrect_answers":["Groin","Chest","Throat"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"What physics principle relates the net electric flux out of a closed surface to the charge enclosed by that surface?","correct_answer":"Gauss&#039;s Law","incorrect_answers":["Faraday&#039;s Law","Ampere&#039;s Law","Biot-Savart Law"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"In physics, conservation of energy and conservation of momentum are both consequences of which of the following?","correct_answer":"Noether&#039;s Theorem","incorrect_answers":["Bell&#039;s Theorem","Wick&#039;s Theorem","Carnot&#039;s Theorem"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"What common name is given to the medial condition, tibial stress syndrome (MTSS)?","correct_answer":"Shin Splints","incorrect_answers":["Tennis Elbow","Carpal Tunnel","Housemaid&#039;s Knee"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which major extinction event was caused by an asteroid collision and eliminated the majority of non-avian dinosaurs?","correct_answer":"Cretaceous-Paleogene","incorrect_answers":["Triassic&ndash;Jurassic","Permian&ndash;Triassic","Ordovician&ndash;Silurian"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which horizon in a soil profile consists of bedrock?","correct_answer":"R","incorrect_answers":["O","B","D"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"What is the most potent toxin known?","correct_answer":"Botulinum toxin","incorrect_answers":["Ricin","Cyanide","Asbestos"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"The word &quot;science&quot; stems from the word &quot;scire&quot; meaning what?","correct_answer":"To know","incorrect_answers":["To measure","To live","To count"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"On the Beaufort Scale of wind force, what wind name is given to number 8?","correct_answer":"Gale","incorrect_answers":["Storm","Hurricane","Breeze"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"All of the following human genetic haplogroup names are shared between Y-chromosome and mitochondrial DNA haplogroups EXCEPT:","correct_answer":"Haplogroup U","incorrect_answers":["Haplogroup L","Haplogroup T","Haplogroup J"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which of the following is NOT a real element?","correct_answer":"Vitrainium","incorrect_answers":["Praseodymium","Hassium","Lutetium"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which of the following plastic is commonly used for window frames, gutters and drain pipes?","correct_answer":"Polyvinylchloride (PVC) ","incorrect_answers":["Polyethylene (PE)","Polypropylene (PP)","Polystyrene (PS)"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"The &#039;Islets of Langerhans&#039; is found in which human organ?","correct_answer":"Pancreas","incorrect_answers":["Kidney","Liver","Brain"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"How much radiation does a banana emit?","correct_answer":"0.1 Microsievert","incorrect_answers":["0.3 Microsievert","0.5 Microsievert","0.7 Microsievert"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"In quantum physics, which of these theorised sub-atomic particles has yet to be observed?","correct_answer":"Graviton","incorrect_answers":["Z boson","Tau neutrino","Gluon"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which moon is the only satellite in our solar system to possess a dense atmosphere?","correct_answer":"Titan","incorrect_answers":["Europa","Miranda","Callisto"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"How many protons are in an oxygen atom?","correct_answer":"Eight","incorrect_answers":["Four","Two","Six"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"Which of the following liquids is least viscous? Assume temperature is 25&deg;C.","correct_answer":"Acetone","incorrect_answers":["Water","Mercury","Benzene"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"How many legs is it biologically impossible for a centipede to have?","correct_answer":"100","incorrect_answers":["26","50","74"]},{"type":"multiple","difficulty":"hard","category":"Science &amp; Nature","question":"What was the first organic compound to be synthesized from inorganic compounds?","correct_answer":"Urea","incorrect_answers":["Propane","Ethanol","Formaldehyde"]}]}